A Guide to the Governor William H. Cabell Executive Papers, 1805-1808
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Chesapeake-Leopard Affair
  - 1807
    - July
      - 1-7 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 8-10 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 11-15 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - 16-19 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - 20-22 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - 23-28 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - 29-31 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - August
      - 1-6 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - 7-15 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - 17-31 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - September (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - October (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - November (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Oversized (Clamshell Box)
  - 1805
    - Dec. 21 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1806
    - Jan. 4 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Jan. 22 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - March 10 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - March 29 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - April 18 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - May 6 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - June 16 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - June 23 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Aug. 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Sept. 13 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Sept. 27 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Oct. 23 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1807
    - Jan. 20 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Jan. 20 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Jan. 21 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - March 9 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - March 19 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - March 26 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - March 31 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - April 16 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - June 20 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - July 25 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Aug. 7 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Sept. 21 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Dec. [N.D.] (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 1808
    - Jan. 5 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Feb. 15 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - March 19 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - March 21 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - June 2 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - June 4 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - June 25 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - July 8 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - July 22 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Aug. 14 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Aug. 22 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Oct. - Pardons - Gillespie, Thomas (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Chesapeake-Leopard Affair, 1807
    - June 24 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - June 25 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - July 10 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - July 15 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Aug. 2 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Aug. 5 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Aug. 22 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Aug. 31 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1806
    - March 8 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Aug. 30 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1807
    - April 30 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1808
    - Jan. 5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Jan. 20 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - April 25 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Sept. 11 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Sept. 30 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Chesapeake-Leopard Affair, 1807
    - July 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - July 4 (Box 11, Folder 10)